- Did you guys do it?
- No. We just made out a little.
(Penny:)Oh, look at you, you bad boy.
(Penny:)- Did you tell her about Priya?
- Uh, I was gonna...
(Leonard:)...but there were too many tongues
in my mouth.
(Penny:)That's gross.
Here's the thing. Uh, I... I'm not one
of those guys who sneaks around...
(Leonard:)...and sleeps with
more than one woman.
(Penny:)Well, good for you.
(Leonard:)The problem is
I wanna be one of those guys.
(Penny:)So sleep with the new girl
and lie to Priya.
(Leonard:)Oh, that's not who I am.
(Sheldon:)All right.
Then break it off with the new girl.
(Leonard:)Now, let's not do anything rash.
She's really hot.
(Penny:)If you like this girl so much,
just end things with Priya.
(Leonard:)Priya and I are in love.
I think we could get married someday.
(Penny:)You're looking for a way
to sleep with both women...
(Penny:)- ...and have everybody be happy about it.
- Now we're getting somewhere.
(Penny:)What does your gut tell you?
"Go ask Penny.
She'll know what to do."